Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXXVI is arranged in 52 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXXVI. 1931 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 437-0. 1931 Convention Resolutions. General
    - Un-Numbered Resolutions., 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Resolutions, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 2)
    - General, 1933-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 437-3. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 3
    - Free Transportation for Express Employees, 1931-1935 (Box 599b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 437-8. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 8
    - Jurisdictional Dispute, Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1931-1937 (Box 599b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 437-9. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 9
    - Jurisdictional Dispute, Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1937 (Box 599b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 437-14. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 14
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 437-15. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolutions Nos. 15-21; Resolution No. 23
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 437-22. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 22
    - World Peace, 1931-1935 (Box 599b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 437-24. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 24
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 437-25. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 25
    - Bus Regulation, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 437-26. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 26
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 437-27. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 27
    - Jurisdictional Disputes, 1931-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 437-28. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 28
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 437-29. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 29
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 437-30. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 30
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 437-31. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 31
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 437-32. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 32
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1941 (Box 599b, Folder 18)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 19)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1933 (Box 599b, Folder 20)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1932 (Box 599b, Folder 21)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 22)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1932 (Box 599b, Folder 23)
    - Old Age Pensions. Newspaper Clippings, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 24)
    - Old Age Pensions. Newspaper Clippings; Copies of Railway Retirement Insurance Bill, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 437-33. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 33
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 437-34. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 34
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 437-35. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 437-35. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - National Boards of Adjustment, 1931-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 437-36. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 36
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 437-37. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 37
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 437-38. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 38
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 437-39. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 39
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 437-40. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 40
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 437-41. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 41
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 437-42. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 42
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 437-43. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 43
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 437-45. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 45
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 38)
    - Old Age Pensions., 1931-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 437-46. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 46
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 437-47. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 47
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 437-48. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 48
    - General, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 437-49. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 49
    - Consolidation of Railroads; Unemployment Insurance; Workmen's Compensation; Freight Forwarding Companies; Bus and Truck Competition; Five-Day Week; Six-Hour Day; Pension Plan or Retirement Insurance, 1931-1935 (Box 599b, Folder 43)
    - Consolidation of Railroads; Unemployment Insurance; Workmen's Compensation; Freight Forwarding Companies; Bus and Truck Competition; Five-Day Week; Six-Hour Day; Pension Plan or Retirement Insurance, 1935 (Box 599b, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 437-50. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolutions Nos. 50-55
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1931 (Box 599b, Folder 45)
    - General, 1931-1934 (Box 599b, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 437-56. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 56
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 437-57. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 57
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 437-58. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 58
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 437-59. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 59
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 437-60. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 60
    - general, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 437-61. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 61
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 437-62. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolutions Nos. 62 and 63
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 437-65. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 65
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 437-66. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 66
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 437-67. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 67
    - Parcel Post Rates, 1931-1932 (Box 600a, Folder 10-11)
    - Parcel Post Rates, 1933 (Box 600a, Folder 12-13)
  - Sub-Series 437-68. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 68
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 437-69. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 69
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 437-70. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 70
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 437-72. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 72
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 437-73. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 73
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 437-78. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 78
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 437-79. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 79
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 437-80. 1931 Convention Resolutions. Miscellaneous Resolutions.
    - General, 1931 (Box 600a, Folder 21)